alstrasoft.com 2012-09-19

# AlstraSoft - Privacy Policy

**AlstraSoft Privacy Policy**

This policy will let you know:

  1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you
  2. What cookies are and how they are used
  3. How your information is used
  4. Who is collecting your information
  5. With whom your information may be shared
  6. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use, and distribution of your information
  7. The kind of security precautions that are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of your information
  8. How Alstrasoft protects children's privacy
  9. What else you should know about your online privacy

** What personally identifiable information is collected from you**

AlstraSoft collects information in several ways from different parts of our web site.

Some personal information is gathered when you register for some of the demos of AlstraSoft software. During registration, we ask for your name and email address. The system will also ask for your street address, city, state/province, zip/postal code, country, telephone number, and the URL of your web site, although only fields that are marked with an asterisk (*) on the registration field are required. This information is used solely to assist you in navigating the system by automatically filling in certain forms with your information so that you don't have to continually re-enter it. Once you register you are no longer anonymous to AlstraSoft - you have a username and are able to take full advantage of the many offerings of the demo programs.

In addition to registration we may ask you for personal information at other times when using some features of AlstarSoft software demos. If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence. Every page within this web site includes a link to this Privacy Policy.

Back to Top

** What cookies are and how they are used**

As part of offering and providing customizable and personalized services, AlstraSoft may use cookies to store and sometimes track information about you. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Several features of this web site require that you accept cookies in order to work properly.

Generally, we use cookies for the following purposes:

(1) Technical administration of the Web site

(2) Customer administration

(3) Finding problems with our website (technical or content related.)

Advertising networks that serve ads onto this web site may also use their own cookies.

We may also collect IP addresses for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers.

Back to Top

** How your information is used**

The primary goal of AlstraSoft in collecting personal information is to provide you, the user, with a customized experience and to assist your navigation throughout this web site.

Back to Top

** Who is collecting your information**

When you are asked for personal information on this web site, you are sharing that information with AlstraSoft alone, unless it is specifically stated otherwise. However, some activities will, by their very nature, result in your personal information being revealed to other users of the demo programs. 

Back to Top

** With whom your information may be shared**

As a general rule, AlstraSoft will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or under the circumstances described below. Please see the Terms of Service or Use Agreements for each of our products and services for more detailed information about how your personal information may be shared.

AlstraSoft may disclose account information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating the Terms of Service of the AlstraSoft or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) the rights or property of the AlstraSoft, other users of the AlstraSoft, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. AlstraSoft may disclose or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve our products and services.

Back to Top

** What choices are available to you regarding collection, use, and distribution of your information**

If you choose not to register or provide personal information, you can still use most of the features of AstraSoft software demos, but you will not be able to access areas or use features that require registration.

You also have choices with respect to cookies. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. 

The AlstraSoft does not sell or rent user information to anyone. We will notify you at the time of data collection or transfer if your data will be shared with a third party and you will always have the option of not permitting the transfer. If you do not wish to allow your data to be shared, you can choose not to use a particular service.

Back to Top

** The kind of security precautions that are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of your information**

Other than the administrator of this web site or other authorized personnel of the AlstraSoft, you are the only person who has access to your personal information. Your user registration is password-protected to prevent unauthorized access.

We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. AlstraSoft will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. As an extra security precaution, you may want to logoff once you have completed a session when using AlstraSoft software demos. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library or Internet cafe.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, AlstraSoft cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.

Back to Top

** How AlstraSoft protects children's privacy**

AlstraSoft is a general audience web site. Children should always ask a parent for permission before sending personal information to anyone online. AlstraSoft does not share personal information about users under the age of 13 with third parties and we do not sell or rent personal information about any of our users, regardless of age. In addition, AlstraSoft will not send any direct email offers to users who indicate they are under the age of 13.

As a result of the new Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) in the United States, we are required to prohibit children under 13 who reside in the U.S. from posting ads or using any of the other features of our site that require them to submit information via forms. This is due to the onerous reporting and verification requirements that this new law places on web sites that allow children under 13 to submit information via forms. Since we do not have the large, dedicated staff that would be necessary to comply with these requirements, our only option in order to remain in compliance with the law is to prohibit all children under 13 who reside in the U.S. from posting any information via forms on our web site. Therefore, children under 13 who reside in the U.S. should not submit any information via forms on our web site, and if you submit such information, you warrant that you are either over the age of 13 or not located in the U.S. and thus not subject to COPPA.

Back to Top

** What else you should know about your online privacy**

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online through the use of our software demos. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.

Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online.

Back to Top
